♪ Hmm ♪
♪ Hey baby girl, I've been
watching you all day ♪
♪ All day, all day, all day ♪
♪ Man, that thing you got
behind you is amazing ♪
♪ Amazing, amazing, amazing ♪
♪ You make me want to take
you out and let it rain ♪
♪ Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain ♪
♪ I know you got a man, but
this is what you should say ♪
♪ Why don't you tell
him that I'm leavin' ♪
♪ Never looking back again ♪
♪ You found somebody who
does it better than he can ♪
♪ No more making you cry,
no more them gray skies ♪
♪ Girl we flying on the G5, G5 ♪
♪ And we're leavin',
never lookin' back again ♪
♪ So call your shawty and
tell him you found a new man ♪
♪ The one who's so, so fly ♪
♪ The one to keep you high ♪
♪ Have you singing all night, like that ♪
♪ Uh oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Man she gon' be singin' ♪
♪ She gon' be singin' ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Now if I talk it girl you
know that I will walk it out ♪
♪ Walk it out, walk it out, walk it out ♪
♪ Man, I'll put my money,
money where my mouth is ♪
♪ Mouth is, mouth is, mouth is ♪
♪ 'Cause you the baddest little
thing that I've ever seen ♪
♪ Ever seen, ever seen, ever seen ♪
♪ So I'ma ask you one
time, if you got a man ♪
♪ Why don't you tell
him that I'm leavin' ♪
♪ Never looking back again ♪
♪ You found somebody who
does it better than he can ♪
♪ No more making you cry,
no more them gray skies ♪
♪ Girl we flying on the G5, G5 ♪
♪ And we're leavin',
never lookin' back again ♪
♪ So call your shawty and
tell him you found a new man ♪
♪ The one who's so, so fly ♪
♪ The one to keep you high ♪
♪ Have you singing all night, like that ♪
♪ Uh oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Man she gon' be singin' ♪
♪ She gon' be singin',
uh she gon' be singin' ♪
ooh you gon' be singin' ♪
♪ Don't stress, don't
stress, don't stress ♪
♪ Just tell him to the left, left, left ♪
♪ Don't stress, don't
stress, don't stress ♪
♪ Cause we gone, and
we gone, and we gone ♪
♪ No stress, no stress, no stress ♪
♪ Girl you deserve nothin' but the best ♪
♪ Girl you need to tell him that ♪
♪ I'm leavin', never looking back again ♪
♪ You found somebody who
does it better than he can ♪
♪ No more making you cry,
no more them gray skies ♪
♪ Girl we flying on the G5, G5 ♪
♪ And we're leavin',
never lookin' back again ♪
♪ So call your shawty and
tell him you found a new man ♪
♪ The one who's so, so fly ♪
♪ The one to keep you high ♪
♪ Have you singing all night ♪
♪ Like, like, like that ♪
♪ Uh oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Man she gon' be singin' ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Singin' all night
like, like, like that ♪
♪ Uh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Man she gon' be singin' ♪
♪ She gon' be singin',
uh she gon' be singin' ♪
ooh you gon' be singin' ♪